const data = [
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Sergio Kun Aguero", "Harry Kane", "Mohammed Salah"],
    correctAnswer: "Sadio Mane",
  },

  {
    question:
      "With 260 goals, who is the Premier League's all-time top scorer?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Sergio Kun Aguero", "Wayne Rooney", "Robin van Persie"],
    correctAnswer: "Alan Shearer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The fastest goal scored in Premier League history came in 7.69 seconds. Who scored it?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Eden Hazard", "Raheem Sterling", "Luis Nani"],
    correctAnswer: "Shane Long",
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the most hat tricks in Premier League history (12)",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Alan Shearer", "Wayne Rooney", "Thierry Henry"],
    correctAnswer: "Sergio Kun Aguero",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which club has recorded the most defeats in Premier League history?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Aston Villa", "West Ham United", "Newcastle"],
    correctAnswer: "Everton",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the highest attendance at a Premier League match?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["75,554", "79,832", "91.598"],
    correctAnswer: "83,222",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Mohamed Salah became the highest scoring African in the Premier League when he scored against Manchester United in October. Who did he overtake?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Sadio Mane", "Emmannuel Adebayor", "Steven Pienaar"],
    correctAnswer: "Didier Drogba",
  },
  {
    question: "Name the Champions of the 2020/21 season?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Chelsea", "Arsenal", "Liverpool"],
    correctAnswer: "Manchester City",
  },
  {
    question:
      " Which team went an entire season without losing a game in 2003/04?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Chelsea", "Manchester United", "Liverpool"],
    correctAnswer: "Arsenal",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did Aguero score his famous title winning goal against in 2012?",
    incorrectAnswers: ["Chelsea", "Aston Villa", "Everton"],
    correctAnswer: "QPR",
  },
];

export default data;
